<resources>
    <string name="app_name">EcoRunners</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="logout">Logout</string>

    <string name="couriersRates">
            <font size="20"><b>Payment Rates and Info </b></font> "\n\n"
           <font size="18"><b>Rates of pay per shop: </b> </font> "\n\n"
        <font size="16"><b>• Taco Mazama: </b>£4.00 an hour and £1.50 per delivery "\n\n"
        <b>• On Call Shift: </b>15% for orders >£20 and £3 for order less than £20 "\n\n"
        <b>• Ashoka Ashton Lane: </b>£4.00 an hour and £1 per delivery "\n\n"
        <b>• Pickled Ginger: </b>£5.00 an hour and £1 per delivery "\n\n"
        <b>• Byblos: </b>£4.00 per hour £1 per delivery "\n\n"
        <b>• Station Wok: </b>£4.00 an hour and £1 per delivery "\n\n"
        <b>• Chicken Place (G1 and G12): </b>£4.00 an hour and £1 per delivery "\n\n"
        <b>• Rumours: </b>£4.50 per hour and £1 per delivery "\n\n"
        <b>• Masala Twist (Byres and Hope Str): </b>£4.50 an hour and £1 per delivery "\n\n"
        <b>• Mamafubu: </b>£5.00 per hour, £1 per delivery "\n\n"
        <b>• Cafe India: </b>£4.00 per hour and £1.00 per delivery "\n\n"
        <b>• Subway: </b>£5.00 per hour, £1.00 per delivery "\n\n"
        <b>• Ushas: </b>£5.00 per hour, £1.oo per delivery (to be confirmed) </font>
    </string>

    <string name="spareBicycleRecord"><font size="20"><b><u>Spare Bikes Log and Info</u></b></font> "\n\n"
    <font size="18"><b><u>Rules: </u></b></font> "\n\n"

    <b>1. <u>ALWAYS</u> update the log when you borrow and return a bike "\n"
    2. Return the bike in the same state that it was when you took it "\n"
    3. <u>ALWAYS</u> inform a team-leader when you need/take a spare"\n"
    4. <u>DON’T</u> keep any bike for more than 3 days ( BUT special circumstances will be considered) </b>
        More details at the end of the document."\n\n"

        <font size="18"><b><u> Spares: </u></b></font> "\n\n"

    <b> 1. Red Roadbike (multispeed) </b> "\n\n"
    • Currently used by: AVAILABLE "\n"
    • Location: Taco Mazama Byres road, rear cupboard (through the toilet room) "\n"
    • Details: S-M frame; thin tyres; flat handlebars; good condition except weak brakes "\n\n"
    <b> 2. Blue Singlespeed </b> "\n\n"
    • Currently used by: Falah Hamza "\n"
    • Location: Chicken Place G12, downstairs "\n"
    • Details: L frame, medium tyres, flat handlebars, good condition - fairly sluggish "\n\n"

    <b> 3. Black Raleigh Singlespeed </b> "\n\n"
    • Currently used by: Nikos Iplik "\n"
    • Location: n/a "\n"
    • Details: L frame, thin-medium tyres, flat handlebars, good condition (tight brakes) "\n\n"

    <b>4. Silver GT Mountainbike (multispeed) </b> "\n\n"
    • Currently used by: AVAILABLE "\n"
    • Location: Mamafubu, downstairs "\n"
    • Details: M frame, thick tyres, flat handlebars, rear mudguards, good condition (back brake handle needs to be fixed) "\n\n"

    <font size="18"><b><u> Relevant info: </u></b></font>  "\n\n"
    <b>• Update the log by writing your name in the ‘currently used by’ section when you borrow a bike, and deleting that and
        writing ‘AVAILABLE’ instead when returning a bike. This document can only be edited from a desktop, not from mobile
        version of facebook </b> "\n"
    <b> • The ‘Location’ section specifies where the bike normally resides, that is if it is not being used by someone
        (in which case it would be with that person, and not at the specified location, of course) </b> "\n"
    <b>• You can use these bikes for free as long as you don’t break them; any damage you do you have to repair yourself
        (wear and tear set aside; eg. you won’t have to fix it if the chain snaps BUT you will have to if you get a puncture)</b> "\n"
    <b>• This is meant for emergency situations, eg. if your own bike breaks during a shift or if it breaks before a shift and you
        don’t have the time/means to repair it. <u>SPARES ARE NOT to act as a permanent/long-term substitute</u> for your bike, hence the
        3 days return limit (but do inform your teamleader if you can’t get your own bike fixed in 3 days due to
        objective reasons - exceptions will be granted) </b> "\n"
    <b>• If you need a spare quickly during your shift you can go get an avaialable spare from one of the locations
        - we highly appreciate couriers having initiative and solving problems independtly - BUT do send a quick text to your
        team leader (eg.: ‘derailleur problem. Getting the blue spare’), so we know what is going on </b> "\n"
    <b>• When picking up a spare from one of the shops please be respectful to the staff; always
        introduce yourself and ask for permission (and instructions) to pick up the spare bike
        (eg.: ‘Hi, I’m an Ecorunners courier, I’d like to pick up the spare you have in the shop, could you please show me...’) </b>"\n"
        <b>   For any questions, suggestions or feedback, message me (Casian). </b>

    </string>

    <string name="shopsGuides"><font size="20"><b><u> Ashoka info </u></b></font> "\n\n\n"
    <font size="18"><b> 1) Basics </b> </font> "\n\n"
    · Be on time; "\n"
    · Don’t go in through the main door; use the side (emergency exit..) door;"\n"
    · Avoid entering the restaurant area; if you have reason to do so, please let the staff know of your intention."\n\n"
    <font size="18"><b> 2) Doing deliveries </b> </font> "\n\n"
    · Keep an eye on the area where they post deliveries"\n"
    · If it’s your delivery to take check where it is in advance"\n"
    · When is it “your delivery to take”? When you are the only courier in the shop, or when you were in the shop before
        the other courier/driver. Rule: first in, first out"\n"
    · Always write the details of the delivery you’re doing (delivery id, postcode, customer number, your name, time you left with
        it time you came back) in the notebook provided"\n"
    <b>· Keep all the delivery slips for cash up at the end of your shift </b> "\n"
    · If the driver (Jim) is working with you, you should leave <b>(whenever possible)</b> all G13s and G14s for <b>him</b> to take"\n"
    • It’s not possible to leave the G13s and G14s to the driver if the driver just left and would take a long time to come back
        or if the delivery is running late (check acceptance time on slip) "\n"
    · If you have to do a delivery that’s more than 3 miles of cycling away, you’ll get paid £2 instead of £1; when this happens
        write “&lt;3 m” in the notebook next to the postcode. When posting your number of deliveries and hours in Ashoka at the end
        of the week make sure you tell us how many deliveries were >3 miles and how many were normal "\n"
    · Check if delivery is paid; if unpaid make sure you have change accordingly "\n"
    · If you don’t have change you can ask the restaurant for a ‘float’ (usually £5) - but try to bring your own "\n"
    · Keep all the cash you receive from customers during your shift - you’ll give it back to the restaurant at the end of your shift,
        when you cash up "\n"
    · Speed: you should aim at delivering within 20 minutes of when you picked the delivery up "\n"
    · You may take multiple deliveries at once if it makes sense to do so (check the addresses!) "\n\n"
    <font size="18"><b> 3) Other stuff  </b> </font> "\n\n"
    · Anything problematic that happens to you or your bike during your shift, any problems that you don’t know how to solve:
        <b>contact your teamleader/write on the ecorunners chat, contact Manos or Elina.</b> You are not alone!"\n"
    · Order your food at least 20 minutes before your shift ends so you don’t have to wait "\n"
    · If you happen to lose one of your slips you can replace it with the kitchen copy - ask some of the staff
        (but they don’t like this happening) "\n"
    · If the restaurant is quiet, you can go (try to) cash up 15 minutes before the official end of your shift "\n\n"
    <font size="18"><b> 4) Background info </b> </font> "\n\n"
    · You can see three types of delivery slips in Ashoka: JustEat, phone restuarant order slip and website restaurant order slip.
        Each of them can be either paid or unpaid. The paid phone ones will have a card receipt stapled to their back so check for
        that. Restaurant website ones are very rare."\n"
    · During the weekdays there are 2 couriers working in Ashoka. During the weekends there are two couriers + a driver "\n"
    · Jim is the driver. He’s quite friendly and sassy. His number is 07880717402 - you can use this to check when he’s coming back,
        so you know if you must take the G13/G14 yourself or not "\n"
    · G13s and G14 are generally quite far away (at least 2 miles, up to 4), and this is why it’s more efficient for the car
        to take them. G20s can ocassionally be nasty as well, but they are usually as good as the other nice postcodes: G11s and G12s "\n"
    · Chetan (guy with an earpiece and suit) is the restaurant manager. Try not to cross him, he’s not always fun "\n"
    · Rates are: £4/hour and £1 or £2/ delivery (£2 if it’s over 3 miles) "\n\n"
    <font size="18"><b> · DO’s </b> </font> "\n\n"
    <b>• - Communicate with your team leader, Manos, Elina, other couriers </b>"\n"
    <b>• - Ask us questions when you’re unsure about something </b>"\n"
    <b>• - Be polite </b>"\n"
    <b>• - Try to be nice with the people you deliver food to </b>"\n"
    <b>• - Be proud to represent EcoRunners </b>"\n"
    <b>• - Assume responsibility and make your own decisions when appropriate </b>"\n"
    <b>• - Stay calm when the restaurant get crazy busy with deiveries. If it’s undoable, then it’s not your responsibility to do
        it (i.e. you’re the only courier and 4 deliveries come at once) </b>"\n"
    <b>• -Ride safe!! </b> "\n\n"

    <font size="18"><b>· DON’T’s </b> </font> "\n\n"
    <b>• · randomly walk in the customer area  </b>"\n"
    <b>• · stay in the way of waiters or any Ashoka staff  </b>"\n"
    <b>• · leave the restaurant/your shift without permission  </b>"\n"
    <b>• · be late for the start of your shift </b>"\n"
    <b>• · ride at night time without lights  </b>"\n"
    <b>• · get into an argument with any of the Ashoka stuff – any problems, you let us know  </b>"\n"
    <b>• · lose delivery slips  </b>"\n"
        "\n\n"


      <font size="20"><b>  Pickled Ginger Info </b> </font> "\n\n"
    1. For pickled ginger you are going to work for multiple shops. Namely la rotunda, yen, diner (all in the same building next
        to hydro), pickled ginger (st vincent st), athena (elderslie street), central sushi (renfield street) "\n"
    2. You are going to need a fully charged smart phone with internet data and also carry a charger or a power bank with you.
        Every shop has wifi, ask the guys to give you the password. B,ut you are going to need data so you can keep an eye on the
        feed when you are not in a shop "\n"
    3. If you have not worked there before, get to PG a bit earlier so they can explain you how they work. You are going to be added
        in a Whats App feed. All info for deliveries are coming through that feed. You are going to be specifically allocated to a
        delivery from the controller (Example: John on bike pick up PG G2) "\n"
    4. When you start your shift post something like " John from Ecorunners starting my shift" so the controller can know "\n"
    5. When you pick up the delivery you mention the shop, the post code and the word "away" (eg PG G2 away)-make note that for
        deliveries from yen you also need to write your name on the slips that stay in the shop "\n"
    6. When you drop the delivery you post clear (eg PG G2 clear) "\n"
    7. 30 minutes before you finish your shift post that you got 30 minutes left. They either going to give you a last close
        by delivery or tell you to cash up. Ask for food ahead of schedule as well to make sure is going to be ready. Usually the
        controller sends orders for staff in a feed "\n"
    8. You keep all the slips with you till the end of the shift. You cash up in PG. if they tell you to go back to every shop to
        drop the slips you DO NOT. The only reason for going to another shop for cashing up is in the case that you had an unpaid
        delivery and you have to get the money back to the shop "\n"
    9. Usually PG wont give you a cash float so make sure you have your own money, in the rare case of unpaid deliveries. If you have
        no money on you you can ask nicely either in rotunda or PG for cash float, they wont say no "\n"
    10. If they try to pay you the delivery fees you let them know that you are getting paid by Ecorunners so you DO NOT get any
        money for the deliveries from them "\n"
    11. All the bags are kept in rotunda please go by rotunda before you start your shift. In the end of the shift make sure all
        the bags are back in rotunda and ask the guys to lock them in the back cupboard. BAGS SHOULD ALWAYS STAY LOCKED NO BAGS
        SHOULD BE LEFT SOMEWHERE ELSE "\n"
    12. Useful language for the feed PG=pickled ginger, LARO= la rotunda, CS= central sushi, away=delivery picked up, clear=delivery
        dropped"\n"
        "\n\n"


      <font size="20"><b>  Taco Mazama Info </b> </font> "\n\n"

   <b> Evening Shift/Weekend Shift: </b>"\n"
        • ensure that there is a red or blue bag insulated to do deliveries with upon arrival at the start of your shift."\n"
        • stay out the way of customers and conduct yourself in a professional manner while in the shop"\n"
        • ensure the blue or red insulated bag is returned to Taco Mazama at the end of your shift, do not take the bag with you
        at the end of the shift"\n"

   <b> Weekday Morning Shift:</b> "\n"
        • pick up the Westend or Central phone at the start of your shift, test it is working and fully charged"\n"
        • go about your daily business and if the you are called go do a delivery for Taco Mazama"\n"
        • once the shift has finished, return the phone to Taco Mazama"\n"

    </string>


    <string name="declarationRegister"> I am aware and accept that this position is a self-
                                        employed position. For more information about the self
                                        employment please visit the website of the government.
                                        The personal sensitive information that you have provided
                                        are for internal use only and securely protected by our
                                        database.
        </string>>


</resources>
